Artifacts Register, 1879-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
- Banners created for peace demonstration after September 11, 2001 attacks on the World Trade Center in NY and the Pentagon in Washington, D.C., 637; cotton/ polyester
  each square piece of cloth is a different color and carries a different message and they are all stapled to a long piece of purple cloth that was a shirt cut into strips and tied together.
  02A-108
  fair